this tutorial is about the box mechanism
本教程是关于盒子机制的
这是最重要的之一
this tutorial is about the box mechanism
this is one of the most important
建立雕塑的机制
弹出窗口，所以这是一个例子
this is one of the most important
mechanisms for building sculptural
盒子及其工作方式是非常基本的
如果你这样看的话，你会看到
mechanisms for building sculptural
pop-ups so here's an example this is the
实际上是2个平行四边形居中
在中央脊柱上折叠此中央
pop-ups so here's an example this is the
box and the way it works is quite basic
柱子推上盖子盖子推上
至关重要的是
box and the way it works is quite basic
if you look at it this way you can see
然后你有这块加入
两个外边缘
if you look at it this way you can see
it's actually 2 parallelograms centered
这就是将整块东西锁住的原因
形状用于无尽的雕塑
it's actually 2 parallelograms centered
on the central spine fold this central
弹出窗口，哦，我得到了一些简单的信息
这里的，这只是一个基本的
on the central spine fold this central
pillar pushes up the lid the lid pushes
报价免费猫头鹰和猫咪
根据盒子，这是你可以的盒子
pillar pushes up the lid the lid pushes
out the top of the sides this is crucial
看到这是推高枕头的枕头
盖子，这是盖子，然后这些
out the top of the sides this is crucial
and then you have this piece that joins
这些是弯曲的形状
整件到位这是一个
and then you have this piece that joins
the two outer edges
稍微花哨一点，这又是
这是基本的盒子，如果你看的话
the two outer edges
that's what locks the whole piece into
最后，您可以看到有一个支柱
粘在推上盖子的脊柱上
that's what locks the whole piece into
shape this is used in endless sculptural
引擎盖和屋顶，并推动那些
向上推的是盖子
shape this is used in endless sculptural
pop-ups oh I just got a couple of simple
结构顶部的侧面和
那么你知道这是两个
pop-ups oh I just got a couple of simple
ones here and this is a just a basic
最终将整个事物锁定为
形状
ones here and this is a just a basic
quote be free Owl and the Pussycat it's
您将需要一个尺子和一个biro
或类似的东西得分
quote be free Owl and the Pussycat it's
based on the box this is the box you can
胶水和剪刀，所以从得分开始
线这将去对面
based on the box this is the box you can
see here's the pillow that pushes up the
纸这将是你的
粘贴标签就可以了
see here's the pillow that pushes up the
lid this is the lid and then these
三遍，所以你得到一二三
想要脱衣舞娘，所以我们只是做一个
lid this is the lid and then these
curved shapes these are what lock the
非常简单的小盒子，所以这些是
将被削减而不是得分
curved shapes these are what lock the
whole piece into position this is a
线
所以我们就把它画在那里
whole piece into position this is a
slightly more fancy one this is again
一个在那里一个在这里，另外两个在这里
不会这么早就一直上升
slightly more fancy one this is again
this is the basic box if you look at it
当你把它剪下来的时候
用工艺刀代替剪刀
this is the basic box if you look at it
end on you can see there is a pillar
这只是为了提高速度，但您可以使用
你可以使用任何一个，所以就切
end on you can see there is a pillar
glue to the spine that pushes up the lid
这些行，所以您要制作四个
你可能想削减的条
glue to the spine that pushes up the lid
the bonnet and the roof and pushes those
金属尺子，但我通常只是这样做
眼睛，然后修剪这些
the bonnet and the roof and pushes those
up that it's the lids that push out the
所以两个像这样，两个像这样
我们有两个短的
up that it's the lids that push out the
sides of the top of the structure and
两个正方形，每个末端都有一个标签
你有两个长的三个
sides of the top of the structure and
then you know here's the and the two
标签两端的正方形，我们将
折叠所有那些折叠线
then you know here's the and the two
ends that lock the whole thing into
所以这是您的底片
卡完全折痕，然后您
ends that lock the whole thing into
shape
有你的四个步骤
将要使盒子，所以你有
you will need a ruler as well as a biro
两个长的两个短的，所以拿一个
这些长胶条中的一端胶水
you will need a ruler as well as a biro
or something like that to score with and
你胶水，你这一端冲洗胶水
与脊椎，所以就像那样
or something like that to score with and
glue and scissors so start with a scored
你只要折叠一下就可以了
那里真的很舒服
glue and scissors so start with a scored
line this is going to go right across
那就是你现在将其折叠成一个
平仓
line this is going to go right across
the paper this is going to be your
把胶水粘到最上面
折痕很重要
the paper this is going to be your
glueing tabs just go right across do it
关上花瓶，把它打开
得到了一个平行四边形
glueing tabs just go right across do it
three times so you got one two three you
教程5现在您构建相同的东西
在脊椎的另一边，所以你
three times so you got one two three you
want strips so we're just making a
带上其他三个面板条
一端胶水再次与
want strips so we're just making a
really simple small box so these are
脊柱减慢速度然后粘上
该条的另一端放入
really simple small box so these are
going to be cut lines rather than score
它的关闭位置关闭了底座
现在你有两个平行四边形
going to be cut lines rather than score
lines
支持这仍然是不稳定的
此时的结构，如果您要
lines
so we'll just draw it in there there's
想要从中冒出来的东西
中间，如果你想要像
so we'll just draw it in there there's
one there one here and two more in here
在这条过道和猫咪船上蒙面
从盒子中间伸出来
that don't go all the way up so early so
现在是您放进去的机会，如果您
想要现在就坚持下去，否则现在
that don't go all the way up so early so
when you cut it out I'm just going to
将胶水放在中间的表面上
在这里并将这两个背靠背粘在一起
when you cut it out I'm just going to
use a craft knife rather than scissors
这个中心支柱需要很多
压力，所以最好加倍
use a craft knife rather than scissors
and it's just for speed but you can use
厚度卡是否可以向上推
顶部很容易不屈曲
and it's just for speed but you can use
you can use either so just cut along
这仍然是一个不稳定的结构
只是平行四边形，你可以
you can use either so just cut along
these these lines so you're making four
看到它只是在这附近摇摆
其实很早的基础
these these lines so you're making four
strips you might want to cut against the
维多利亚时代的弹出窗口只是
用这样的平行四边形制成
strips you might want to cut against the
metal ruler but I usually just do it by
在页面上方为您提供了浮动平面
但是他们无法稳定
metal ruler but I usually just do it by
eye and then trim these up
摇摆仍然是3d，但不是
刚性结构，那么您可以选择其中之一
eye and then trim these up
so two like that and two like this here
这两个面板和这些棍子
跨越他们附着到平原
so two like that and two like this here
we are got two short ones which are just
而且选项卡去的地方真的没有
重要的是您的设计问题
we are got two short ones which are just
two squares with a tab on each end and
他们可以进入室内或室外
是的，我只是要在
two squares with a tab on each end and
you have two long ones that are three
外面只是为了简单
您可以将胶水放在两个标签上
you have two long ones that are three
squares of the tab on each end and we'll
同时用胶水将它们粘上
只是为了让它变得有趣而已
squares of the tab on each end and we'll
just fold all those those fold lines
这是一个刚性结构，您不需要
仅在另一端需要面板时
so here's your base sheet a single piece
你真的想做一个坚实的
盒子也不必是完整的
so here's your base sheet a single piece
of card thoroughly creased and then you
盒子的高度
然后将两个外平面连接起来
of card thoroughly creased and then you
have your your four step of strips that
它将起作用之间的区别
这些和水上飞机类型
have your your four step of strips that
are going to make the box so you've got
我们在教程中介绍的机制
12是当您关闭底座的盖子时
are going to make the box so you've got
two long ones two short ones so take one
下沉，外端上升，所以
它将阻止您拥有任何东西
two long ones two short ones so take one
of these long ones put glue on one end
向前伸出，你可以有碎片
以这种方式喷射出来的
of these long ones put glue on one end
you glue you glue this one end flush
方式，但在这种情况下，他们不能只是出去
直接从顶部
you glue you glue this one end flush
with the spine so it's like that then
所以现在我将向您展示一个整体
一系列惊人的弹出窗口和弹出窗口
with the spine so it's like that then
you can just fold out just make sure
全部基于的雕塑
这样的盒子，所以这是本书
you can just fold out just make sure
it's really comfortable there so that
是尼克·丹奇（Nick Dench）的《胡桃夹子》
它有一个非常惊人的华丽
it's really comfortable there so that
that's one you now fold it into its
在此展示重要的事情
教程是这块背面的
that's one you now fold it into its
closed position
是盒子，其余的折叠下来
其余全部基于默认值
closed position
put glue glue right up to the up to the
背面保持垂直
它的背面，你可以看到这里的
put glue glue right up to the up to the
crease is quite important
推上盖子的中央支柱
顶部然后盖子推开
crease is quite important
shut the vase open that up now you've
那边的墙顶
所以当它关闭时，您会看到
shut the vase open that up now you've
got a parallelogram this is covered in
起作用，所以那是盒子的一部分
大显示器的一部分，下一个
got a parallelogram this is covered in
tutorial 5 now you build the same thing
想要表明你在咆哮的狮子故事
罗恩·范德米尔（Ron van der Meer）
tutorial 5 now you build the same thing
on the other side of the spine so you
这是一个有趣的变化
圆形变化仍然堆积
on the other side of the spine so you
take your other three panel strip put
向下平行于脊椎的每一侧
但两端更像
take your other three panel strip put
glue on one end glue again flash with
一开始我给你看过的船
当您关闭底座时，您会看到
glue on one end glue again flash with
the spine slows it down and then glue on
盒子的顶部向下沉
从侧面切下一块
the spine slows it down and then glue on
the other end of that strip put it in
所以你可以看到里面你可以看到
中央支柱，实际上有
the other end of that strip put it in
its closed position shut the base okay
上面有一些动作
下一个有趣的雕塑
its closed position shut the base okay
now you've got two parallelograms back
我们有另一个变化
这个人用的方式很棒
now you've got two parallelograms back
to back this is still an unstable
David F的世界弹出式建筑物
史密斯和这个金色的模特
to back this is still an unstable
structure at this point if you're going
门桥
这是基于盒子的，如果你看
structure at this point if you're going
to want something coming up out of the
有一个中央支柱推高了
盖子是桥的甲板和
to want something coming up out of the
middle if you want something like the
然后V一些这些边位
是锁住整个东西的碎片
middle if you want something like the
masked on this aisle and Pussycat boat
形状，使其关闭时您可以看到
盒子的所有组件都在那里
masked on this aisle and Pussycat boat
sticking up from the middle of the box
但这是非常不寻常的
配置接下来我们有Dinah topia
sticking up from the middle of the box
now's your chance to put it in so if you
詹姆斯·古尼（James Gurney）
这是这只恐龙
now's your chance to put it in so if you
want that stick it in now otherwise now
弯曲的形状
教程13它建在表带上
want that stick it in now otherwise now
put glue on on the surface in the middle
这是教程9，在我们关闭它时
你可以看到是推动中心支柱
put glue on on the surface in the middle
here and glue these two back to back
盒子上的盖子在里面
恐龙，然后这些是
here and glue these two back to back
this central pillar takes quite a lot of
将它们保持在一起的侧面
这是建立在顶部的弯曲形状
this central pillar takes quite a lot of
stress so it's good to have it double
盒子并绑在皮带上
事情不在中心
stress so it's good to have it double
thickness card so is it it can push up
书的中心，但偏离到
接下来，我们将看到Hormats弹出书
thickness card so is it it can push up
the top quite easily without buckling
著名的船，这是一个非常美丽的
小波普尔，这很不寻常
the top quite easily without buckling
this is still an unstable structure this
这些盒子设计的通知他们上升
在书的中央脊柱下
this is still an unstable structure this
is just to parallelograms and as you can
这个真的很聪明
如果你看它的话，它会结束
is just to parallelograms and as you can
see it just wobbles around this is
你会看到有柱子升起
从推动甲板的脊椎开始
see it just wobbles around this is
actually the basis of really early
船的两端
将其锁定到位，实际上是ik
actually the basis of really early
pop-ups the Victorian pop-ups were just
确实有一点点
两端都挺直的，不错
pop-ups the Victorian pop-ups were just
made with parallelograms like this which
一点点的设计
这本书是弹出式棋盘游戏，
made with parallelograms like this which
gave you a floating plane above the page
Matt Johnston和
这是我想给你看的那个
gave you a floating plane above the page
but there wasn't stable they could just
如果你看着它是另一艘船
关闭，您会看到那里有一个
but there wasn't stable they could just
wobble around it was still 3d but not a
中间的支柱正在向上推
甲板，然后甲板推
wobble around it was still 3d but not a
rigid structure then you take one of
有趣地从船的侧面
这根桅杆是因为有索具
rigid structure then you take one of
these two panel pieces and these stick
索具卡在
这本书关闭时，船在甲板上
these two panel pieces and these stick
across they attach to the outer Plains
正在下降，但船的侧面
正在上升，所以你不能有桅杆
across they attach to the outer Plains
and where the tabs go really doesn't
卡在索具的顶部，
桅杆卡在底座上，松动了
and where the tabs go really doesn't
matter it's a question of your design
在甲板内上下滑动
下一个是神话般的飞行
matter it's a question of your design
they can go inside or outside and these
机器造纸工程，但如果一分钱
这是一个非常了不起的雕塑
they can go inside or outside and these
yeah I'm just going to do it on the
它是基于整个盒子
一系列的平行四边形，如果你看
yeah I'm just going to do it on the
outside just for simplicity
最后，您会看到有中央
支柱推动将其向上推，然后
outside just for simplicity
you can put glue on both tabs at the
底翼相当于
盒子的盖子，然后只是一个
you can put glue on both tabs at the
same time glue them in glue them on shut
整个平行四边形和这个
在前面的那一部分
same time glue them in glue them on shut
the base just to make it fun now this is
锁定它的形状，但在此
如果这些螺旋桨在
the base just to make it fun now this is
a this is a rigid structure you don't
对角线，因此页面关闭
那些卡在了两个角落
a this is a rigid structure you don't
need the panel on the other end only if
平行四边形进一步分开
当页面关闭时，这些即将到来
need the panel on the other end only if
you're really wanting to make a solid
一起直到你到达右边
位置，然后锁定钩子
you're really wanting to make a solid
box also it doesn't need to be the full
整个事情成型，接下来我们有
威利bollocks
box also it doesn't need to be the full
height of the of the box yeah as long as
maxi的机器，这是最
非同寻常的雕塑集
height of the of the box yeah as long as
it's joining the two outer planes then
这是我要告诉你的那个
大型卡车超越了
it's joining the two outer planes then
it will work the difference between
本教程真的
非凡的内置拉力条
it will work the difference between
these and the floating plane type
当您拉带子陷阱
提起并倾倒内容物
these and the floating plane type
mechanism that we looked at in tutorial
背面的我可以向你展示这个
当您将标签整个拉回
mechanism that we looked at in tutorial
12 is as you close the base the lid
卡车举起并丢下停机坪
或现在真的很特别
12 is as you close the base the lid
sinks down and the outer end comes up so
一个让我去一个漂亮的雕塑
旧线发出一些
sinks down and the outer end comes up so
it will stop you having anything that
chitty-chitty-bang-bang的标志
Paul Taylor的造纸工程，这是
it will stop you having anything that
juts out forward you can have pieces
这辆车又是基于盒子的
如果你看着它结束，你会看到
juts out forward you can have pieces
that are jetting out this way and this
中间有一个支柱
推上盖子盖子在里面
that are jetting out this way and this
way but in this case they can't just out
真的很难看你是否
这样看，您可能会看到
way but in this case they can't just out
directly from the top
里面有盖子
中央支柱向上推，然后
so now I'm going to show you a whole
盖子将侧面推开，然后
汽车的引擎盖越过顶部，所以
so now I'm going to show you a whole
range of amazing pop ups and pop-up
在这些结构上，您必须具有
盖在里面，因为当页面关闭时
range of amazing pop ups and pop-up
sculptures that are all up all based on
这本书合上盖子会掉下来，如果
您想要引擎盖继续弹出
sculptures that are all up all based on
the box like this so this is this book
必须是单独的一块
所以在支柱里面有盖子
the box like this so this is this book
is The Nutcracker by Nick Dench field
中心将盖子推上
推出侧面的墙壁，
is The Nutcracker by Nick Dench field
and it has a really amazing flamboyant
然后这是一个单独的东西
页首接下来，我们有了《绿野仙踪》
and it has a really amazing flamboyant
display the important thing in this
罗伯茨·奥布达（Robertsóbuda），然后在此传播
这个房子是盒子，所以如果你看
display the important thing in this
tutorial is this piece at the back this
最后，您会看到有一个支柱
在这里推高一点，然后
tutorial is this piece at the back this
is the box so as the rest folds down the
这是将两个外部
墙壁，所以这是使用带有
is the box so as the rest folds down the
rest is all based on defaults the box at
书作为背景而不是基础
所以你可以看到
rest is all based on defaults the box at
the back stays stays vertical we look at
这是我展示的原始影片
你，所以你可以看到它关闭盖子
the back stays stays vertical we look at
the back of it you can see here's the
掉下来但锁住它的墙
一切都形成了，所以在
the back of it you can see here's the
central pillar that pushes up the lid on
效果在这种情况下，我们得到的是
这是房子的屋顶
central pillar that pushes up the lid on
the top and then the lid pushes out
当它关闭时就在这里
关闭，您可以看到房子的屋顶
the top and then the lid pushes out
there the top of the walls at the side
上升，所以这边是另一个
另一个有趣的机制是
there the top of the walls at the side
so as it closes you can see how that
我们所看到的自动拉带
在教程16中，所以这是最后一个
so as it closes you can see how that
works so that that's the box is part of
和Brer Rabbit造纸工程
维克多（Victor）/白色，这是我们的
works so that that's the box is part of
a part of a big display the next one I'd
皮带再次，这是
塔
a part of a big display the next one I'd
like to show you is roaring lion tales
这是一个盒子机制，最后
再次在这里，我们再次建立它
like to show you is roaring lion tales
by Ron van der Meer
放在皮带上，这把小马和小推车
这是一个盒子机制，你可以看到结束
by Ron van der Meer
this is an interesting variation this is
在那边，所以你可以看到中央
顶推盖子的支柱
this is an interesting variation this is
a a circular variation is still stacked
推出侧面，这是盒子
这是我的详细处理
a a circular variation is still stacked
down parallel to the spine on each side
书籍弹出式设计和纸张力学
您
down parallel to the spine on each side
but the ends are rounded more like the
您